Alisina Adeel

Asina8403@gmail.com/ Phone #:+93745255104 / Address: Kabul, Afghanistan

PROFESIONAL SUMMARY

I worked as a web developer at GAOTek for one years, also I worked as a database developer with Unisonant Youths' Social Institution for one year. In addition, I build several websites with WordPress, React.js and next.js as a freelancer. Please take a look to my updated portfolio here: https://portfilio-alisina-adeel.vercel.app/

SKILLS

- HTML, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript
- React JS, Next.js, Mongo Db
- Typescript, Node.js

- Problem solving
- Trouble shouting and testing
- Work ethic

WORK HISTORY

Web developer / GAOTek / Online

01/2023-11/2023

- Write well-designed, efficient, and maintainable code using appropriate technologies.
- Develop websites and web applications according to project specifications.
- Implement responsive design principles to ensure a consistent user experience across different devices.
- Create user interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
 Implement and maintain front-end frameworks React and Next.js.

Database Developer /Unisonant Youths' Social Institution/ Kabul 02/2017 – 11/2017

- Design and implement database structures based on the requirements of the application or system.
- Normalize data to reduce redundancy and improve data integrity.
- Define relationships between tables and establish primary and foreign keys.

EDUCATION

Kateb Private University – Kabul, Afghanistan / 2017-2022 **Bachelor degree - Computer science**

Hobbies

- Gamming
- Programming
- Reading and Learning
- Fitness & Music
- Travelling
- Photography

Speak, Read & Write

- Dari
- English
 - Pashto